dealite.in 2018-02-23

# Online Auction Policy, Terms And Condition | Dealite.in Online Auction Site

We value the trust you place in Dealite.in. That's why we work hard to earn your trust & confidence so that you can enthusiastically use our services and recommend us to friends and family. Please read the following statement to learn about our information gathering and dissemination practices.  

Note: To ensure the safety and protection of consumer information, we will continue to review and improve our Privacy Policy and procedures. Our Privacy Policy is subject to change at any time without notice. To make sure you are aware of any changes, please review this policy periodically. By visiting this website you agree to be bound by the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree, please do not use or access our Site.  

1\. Collection of Personally Identifiable Information 

We may collect personally identifiable information from you in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when you visit our site, register on the site, buy bids, buy seat, place an order, co-host auctions with Dealite and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our site. You may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, date of birth, demographic profile, preferences, interests, etc. Our primary goal in doing so is to provide a safe, efficient, smooth and customized experience. You may, however, visit our site anonymously. We will collect personally identification information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. You can always refuse to supply personally identifiable information, except that it may prevent you from engaging in certain site related activities.  

2\. Use of Demographic and Profile Data

We use personal information to provide the services you request. To the extent we use your personal information to market to you, we will provide you the ability to opt-out of such uses. We use your personal information to customize your experience; resolve disputes; troubleshoot problems; help promote a safe service; collect fees owed; measure consumer interest in our products and services, inform you about online and offline offers, products, services, and updates; detect and protect us against error, fraud and other criminal activity; enforce our terms & conditions; and as otherwise described to you at the time of collection.

In our efforts to continually improve our product and service offerings, we collect and analyze demographic and profile data about our users' activity on our website.

We identify and use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our website. Your IP address is also used to help identify you and to gather broad demographic information.

We will occasionally ask you to complete optional online surveys. These surveys may ask you for contact information and demographic information (like pincode, age, or income level). We use this data to tailor your experience at our site, providing you with content that we think you might be interested in and to display content according to your preferences.

Cookies

A "cookie" is a small piece of information stored by a Web server on a Web browser so it can be later read back from that browser. Cookies are useful for enabling the browser to remember information specific to a given user. Dealite.in places both permanent and temporary cookies in your computer's hard drive. To protect your privacy we do not use cookies to store or transmit any personal information about you on the Internet.  

3\. Sharing of personal information 

We use the services of our enabling partners such as outside shipping companies, resellers, business associates to fulfill orders, and credit card processing companies to process the payment for goods and services ordered from Dealite.in website. We will share your information with our Alliance Partners and Affiliates who work with us or on our behalf to help provide you the services.

We may share personal information with our other corporate entities and affiliates to: help detect and prevent identity theft, fraud and other potentially illegal acts; correlate related or multiple accounts to prevent abuse of our services; and to facilitate joint or co-branded services that you request where such services are provided by more than one corporate entity and/ or affiliate. Those entities and affiliates may not market to you as a result of such sharing unless you explicitly opt-in.

We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to court orders or other legal processes. We may disclose personal information to law enforcement offices, third party rights owners, or others in the good faith belief that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to: enforce our Terms & Conditions or Privacy Policy; respond to claims that an advertisement, posting or other content violates the rights of a third party; or protect the rights, property or personal safety of our users or the general public.

Dealite.in and its affiliates will share some or all of your personal information with another business entity should we (or our assets) plan to merge with, or be acquired by that business entity. Should such a transaction occur then that other business entity (or the new combined entity) may be required to follow this Privacy Policy with respect to your personal information.

4\. Links to Other Sites

Our site links to other websites that may collect personally identifiable information about you. Dealite.in is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those linked websites.  

5\. Security Precautions

Our site has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.  

6\. Choice/Opt-Out

Dealite.in provides all users with the opportunity to opt-out of receiving non-essential (promotional, marketing-related) communications from us on behalf of our partners, and from us in general, after setting up an account.

To remove your contact information from all Dealite.in lists and newsletters, please contact us at the address provided below.

7\. Advertisements on Dealite.in

We may use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.  

8\. Questions

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to the following address: [](mailto:support@dealite.in)support@dealite.in
